A Guide to the Agricultural Development Council records, Record Group 2 FA1440
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Board of Trustees Files, 1955-1981; 3; 0.95 Cubic Feet 2 letter document boxes and 1 half-box
  - Agricultural Development Council Board of Trustees - Interim Actions, 1959-1967 (Box 80, Folder 1)
  - Agricultural Development Council Board of Trustees - Agendas and Minutes, 1977-1978 (Box 80, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural Development Council Board of Trustees - Agendas and Minutes, 1979 (Box 81, Folder 1)
  - Report on Indonesia - Arthur Goodfriend, 1955 (Box 81, Folder 2)
  - Agricultural Development Council Board of Trustees - Agendas and Minutes, 1980-1981 (Box 276, Folder 1-2)
- John D. Rockefeller 3rd Files, 1954-1961; 4; 1.52 Cubic Feet 4 letter document boxes
  - The Council on Economic and Cultural Affairs (CECA) - Board of Trustees Meetings (JDR 3rd copies), 1954-1956 (Box 81, Folder 3)
  - The Council on Economic and Cultural Affairs (CECA) - Board of Trustees Meetings (JDR 3rd copies), 1957-1959 (Box 82, Folder 1-4)
  - The Council on Economic and Cultural Affairs (CECA) - Board of Trustees Meetings (JDR 3rd copies), 1959-1960 (Box 83, Folder 1-5)
  - The Council on Economic and Cultural Affairs (CECA) - Board of Trustees Meetings (JDR 3rd copies), 1960-1961 (Box 84, Folder 1-3)
- Grants, 1956-1981; 5; 9.77 Cubic Feet 22 letter document boxes and 3 legal document boxes
  - Core Program, Core Budget Grants, and Completed Grants, 5.1
    - Indian Agricultural Research Institute (66-143-1-16_, 1966-1975 (Box 85, Folder 1)
      Scope and Contents
      Three Year Program to strengthen the division of agricultural economics
    - Chung Ho Kim (72-14-21), 1972-1976 (Box 85, Folder 2)
      Travel grant for research assistant at Michigan State University
    - Science University of Malaysia, School of Comparative Social Sciences (72-14-28), 1972-1976 (Box 85, Folder 3)
    - Nihal Amerasinghe (72-14-40), 1972-1977 (Box 85, Folder 4)
      Support toward PhD at Wye College (University of London)
    - An-tien Hsieh (73-14-38), 1973-1975 (Box 85, Folder 5)
      Travel grant to accept scholarship from Harvard
    - Choong Yong Ahn, 1974 (Box 85, Folder 6)
    - Bellagio Conference on Agriculture in Development Theory, 1973 May (Box 85, Folder 7)
    - Ying-chich Chiang (73-14-42), 1973 (Box 85, Folder 8)
      Travel grant to return to NTU in Taipei
    - Chikliaiah Naicker College (73-14-15), 1973 (Box 85, Folder 9)
      Study of Agro-Industrial Integration
    - University of Malaysia (73-14-17), 1973 (Box 86, Folder 1)
      Land and Peasants in Malaysia
    - Rogelio Cuyno (73-14-24), 1973 (Box 86, Folder 2)
      Travel grant for dissertation research
    - Association of Colleges of Agriculture in the Philippines (ACAP) (74-14-13), 1974 (Box 86, Folder 3)
      In Service Training
    - Association of Colleges of Agriculture in the Philippines (ACAP) (74-14-14), 1974 (Box 86, Folder 4)
      Workshop on Testing for Guidance Counselors
    - Association of Colleges of Agriculture in the Philippines (ACAP) (74-14-15), 1974 (Box 86, Folder 5)
      Institutional Management, Case Studies
    - Narciso R. Deomampo (74-14-24), 1974 (Box 86, Folder 6)
      Travel Grant
    - Fund for the International Conference of Agricultural Economists 1976 (74-18-7), 1974-1976 (Box 86, Folder 7)
      Interim Expenses of Conferences, Arrangements
    - Tirath Gupta (74-14-21), 1974 (Box 86, Folder 8)
      Travel grant for repatriation to India
    - Institut Pertainian Bogor (74-14-22), 1974-1975 (Box 86, Folder 9)
      74-75 Post Graduate Workshop Support
    - Mu-Keun Lee (74-14-31), 1974 (Box 86, Folder 10)
      Travel grant to accept assistantship from University of Illinois
    - Kasetsart University (73-14-6), 1973-1975 (Box 86, Folder 11)
      Rector Chakrabandhu Travel
    - Kasetsart University, Rural Education Department, Socioeconomic Studies (69-14-43), 1969 (Box 86, Folder 12)
    - Cheng-hung Liao (74-14-25), 1974 (Box 87, Folder 1)
      Repatriation travel grant for return to Taiwan
    - Oregon State University (73-14-1), 1973 (Box 87, Folder 2)
      Yu-shin Kao support for the completion of PhD program
    - M. A. Oommen (74-14-18), 1974 August (Box 87, Folder 3)
      Travel Grant for Sri Lanka Conference
    - W. M. J. Perera (74-18-26), 1974 (Box 87, Folder 4)
      Travel for observation of United States Projects
    - RTN Nutrition Seminar, Princeton, NJ, 1973 November (Box 87, Folder 5)
    - Saisuree Chutikul (74-18-28), 1974 (Box 87, Folder 6)
    - Vimal P. Shah (74-18-27), 1974 (Box 87, Folder 7)
      Travel for RTN Seminar
    - Dr. Sudjanadi R. (74-18-20), 1974 (Box 87, Folder 8)
      Training program in regional planning in the Netherlands
    - Ministry of Agriculture and Cooperatives, Thailand (74-14-8), 1974 (Box 87, Folder 9)
      In-Service Training Program
    - University of the Philippines (75-14-7), 1975 (Box 87, Folder 10)
      Workshop-Seminar on Teaching and Research
    - Mahar Mangahas (75-18-18), 1975 August (Box 87, Folder 11)
      Travel grant for the Third World Congress of the Econometric Society
    - Sudhin K. Mukhopadhyay (75-18-26) - Third World Congress of Econometric Society, 1975 August (Box 87, Folder 12)
    - Andalas University (75-14-5), 1975 (Box 88, Folder 1)
      Rice farmers response to new technology
    - Andhra University (75-14-1), 1975 (Box 88, Folder 2)
      Research by Prasad Rao
    - Kong Nam Hyun (75-14-33), 1975 (Box 88, Folder 3)
      Travel grant to accept assistanceship at Ohio State University
    - Dr. G. Parthasarathy (75-14-12), 1975 (Box 88, Folder 4)
      Visiting professorship at Cornell University
    - Leodagario M. Ilag (75-18-40), 1975 (Box 88, Folder 5)
      Travel grant
    - Institut Pertanian Bogor (75-14-11), 1975 (Box 88, Folder 6)
      Scholarships for M.S. studies
    - Francis Chan (75-14-24), 1975 (Box 88, Folder 7)
      Travel grant for completion of dissertation at Stanford
    - Syiah Kuala University (75-14-6), 1975 (Box 88, Folder 8)
      Home Industry as Secondary Source of Farmers Income
    - R. R. Appadurai (76-18-27), 1976 (Box 88, Folder 9)
      Travel grant for United States professional visits
    - A. S. Charan (76-14-10), 1976 (Box 88, Folder 10)
      Travel grant for IDS seminar on irrigation.
    - Gadjah Mada University (75-14-13), 1975 (Box 88, Folder 11)
      Post-Grad course in Agricultural Economics
    - Gadjah Mada University (75-14-25), 1975 (Box 89, Folder 1)
      Post-Grad Agricultural Extension course
    - University of the Philippines (76-14-37), 1976 (Box 89, Folder 2)
      Summer program in economics
    - W. R. D. Nilaweera (76-14-31), 1976 (Box 89, Folder 3)
    - Mahmood Hasan Khan (77-14-23), 1977 (Box 89, Folder 4)
      Repatriation to Pakistan
    - P. S. Majumdar (76-14-5), 1976 (Box 89, Folder 5)
      Travel grant, University
    - Eu-Gak Hwang (76-14-29), 1976 (Box 89, Folder 6)
      Travel to return to Korea
    - Kasetsart University, Home Economics Department (76-14-24), 1976 (Box 89, Folder 7)
      Seminar on Role of Home Economics in National Development
    - J. L. Kaul, 1975-1976 (Box 89, Folder 8)
    - Dean Phoonphon Asanachianta (76-14-32) (Box 89, Folder 9)
      Travel grant for professional visits
    - International Conference of Agricultural Economists (IAAE) - 1976 Conference (Box 89, Folder 10)
    - N. R. Deomampo (76-14-9), 1976 (Box 90, Folder 1)
      Post-Doctoral year at Minnesota
    - Gadjah Mada University (76-14-21), 1976 (Box 90, Folder 2)
      Post-Grad workshop in agricultural economics
    - Ngo Quoc Trung (77-14-16), 1977 August (Box 90, Folder 3)
      Travel grant for the Fifth World Congress of Economics, Yokyo
    - Silliman University (77-14-8), 1977 (Box 90, Folder 4)
      Maturan Travel Grant
    - Silliman University (77-14-22), 1977 (Box 90, Folder 5)
      Travel grant for professor Chiong
    - Sopin Tongpay (76-14-23), 1976 (Box 90, Folder 6)
      Travel grant for participation in World Food Conference at Iowa State University
    - Supranee Rungdanay (75-14-16), 1975 (Box 90, Folder 7)
      Travel grant to return to Kasetsart University.
    - University of Sussex (77-18-14), 1977 (Box 90, Folder 8)
      Study on the role of women in rural development
    - Nimal Ranaweera (77-14-5), 1977 (Box 90, Folder 9)
      Dissertation research support
    - Rusli Said (75-14-36), 1975 (Box 90, Folder 10)
      Travel grant for visit to Pakistan Academy of Rural Development
    - Upali Nanayakkara (76-14-30), 1976 (Box 90, Folder 11)
      Grant for the completion of PhD program at Michigan State University
    - University of Wisconsin (75-14-35), 1975-1976 (Box 90, Folder 12)
      Sathyapala Research Support
    - Saburo Yamada (75-18-39), 1975 November 13-14 (Box 91, Folder 1)
      Travel grant for NBER Conference participation
    - Diponegoro University, Research and Development Center (78-14-6), 1978 (Box 91, Folder 2)
      Workshop in research methodology
    - University of New England (77-14-21), 1977 (Box 91, Folder 3)
      I. J. Singh Post Doctoral Year
    - Cecilia A. Florencio (77-18-15), 1977 (Box 91, Folder 4)
      Travel grant for participation in RTN Seminar
    - Gadjah Mada University (77-14-11), 1977 (Box 91, Folder 5)
      PhD program support
    - Bangladesh Agricultural Economists Association (79-14-10), 1979 (Box 96, Folder 1)
      Publication of Proceedings of First Meetings
    - Bogor Agricultural University (78-14-12), 1978 (Box 96, Folder 2)
      Remedial Program in Economic Theory
    - Bungaran Saragih (80-14-1), 1980 (Box 96, Folder 3)
    - Agha Sajjad Haider (78-14-13), 1978 (Box 96, Folder 4)
      Travel grant for professional visits to FAO
    - Agro-Economic Survey (75-14-38), 1975 (Box 96, Folder 5)
      Workshop on Resettlement and Conservation
    - Sabri Ahmad (80-14-3), 1980 (Box 96, Folder 6)
      Travel grant for special course at Rhode Island
    - Torng-Chuang Wu (78-14-4), 1978 (Box 96, Folder 7)
      Support for completion of PhD at Davis
    - Association of College of Agriculture in the Philippines (77-14-10), 1977 (Box 96, Folder 8)
    - University of Minnesota (70-14-20), 1970 (Box 96, Folder 9)
      V. S. Vyas visiting professorship
    - Repatriation Program for Asian Social Scientists, 1972-1976 (Box 96, Folder 10)
    - Luechai Chulasai (75-14-32), 1975 (Box 97, Folder 1)
      Travel grant to accept assistantship at University of Illinois
    - University of the Philippines (78-14-12), 1978 (Box 97, Folder 2)
      1978 Summer Program in Economics
    - Young-Key Ro (76-14-8), 1976 (Box 97, Folder 3)
      Travel grant for transportation to Ohio State University
    - Satya Wacana University (75-14-28), 1975 (Box 97, Folder 4)
      Regency Program Management and its Impact on Villages
    - Suhud Tjakrawerdja (76-14-12), 1976 (Box 97, Folder 5)
      University of Michigan, Survey Research Techniques Summer Course
    - Thiravet Pramuanratkarn (77-14-6), 1977 (Box 97, Folder 6)
      PhD completion at the University of Washington
    - Davendra Singh Tyagi (Box 97, Folder 7)
    - Diponegoro University (80-14-12), 1980 (Box 97, Folder 8)
      Role of Women in Food Production
    - East-West Center (80-14-11), 1980 (Box 97, Folder 9)
      Partial support for fifth rural sociology congress
    - Gadjah Mada University (79-14-6) - Suparmoko Dissertation Research (79-14-6), 1979 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Institut Pertainian Bogor (74-14-22), 1974 (Box 97, Folder 11)
      M.S. Scholarship support
    - Kamphol Adulavidhaya - Travel Grant (79-14-11), 1979 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Wegeri Jember University (80-14-13), 1980 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Dae Hee Song (77-14-7), 1977 (Box 98, Folder 2)
      Travel to Penn State for assistanceship
    - Chul Ho Yoo (79-14-1), 1979 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Bangladesh Journal of Agricultural Economics (80-14-4), 1980 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Brawijaya University (80-14-14), 1980 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - Effendi Pasandaran (81-14-01), 1981 (Box 98, Folder 6)
      Travel grant for period at Rutgers University
    - Hasanuddin University (80-14-10), 1980 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Malaysian Agricultural Economists Association (80-14-2), 1980 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - University of Agriculture, Faisalabad (79-14-3), 1979 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Agricultural Economists Research Institute (73-14-41), 1973 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Agricultural Projects Services Centre - Photocopy Equipment (77-14-4), 1977 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Agricultural Projects Services Centre - Equipment Grant (76-14-3), 1976 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Agricultural Projects Services Centre - Books for the Library (75-14-37), 1975 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Ateneo De Davao University - Books for the Library (74-14-10), 1974 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Ateneo de Naga University (73-14-9), 1973 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Bangladesh Agricultural Research Institute - Book Grant (79-14-8), 1979 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Bangladesh Agricultural Institute (73-14-40), 1973 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - Bangladesh Rice Research Institute - Books for Library (75-14-7), 1975 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - Nepal Projects (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - Philippine Projects (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - Sri Lanka Projects (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - Brawijaya University (79-15-5), 1979 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - 1971 Budgets (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - 1972 Budgets (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - 1973 and 1974 Budgets, 1973-1974 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - 1975 Budgets (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - 1976 Budgets (Box 100, Folder 3A)
    - 1977 Budgets (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - 1978 Budgets (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - 1979 Budgets (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Chiengmai University (73-14-36), 1973 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Chittagong University - Book Grant (76-14-1), 1976 (Box 101, Folder 3)
      Department of Economics
    - Divine World University of Tacloban - Book Grant (73-14-8), 1973 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Economic Research Institute, Pakistan (80-14-7), 1980 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Himachal Pradesh University - Book Grant (78-14-3), 1978 (Box 101, Folder 6)
      Agro-Economic Research Center
    - Jember University - Book Grant (77-14-9), 1977 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - University of North Sumatra - Book Grant (77-14-3), 1977 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Institute of Philippine Culture (72-14-1), 1972 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Notre Dame University (73-14-10), 1973 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - University of the Philippines - Book Grant (74-14-19), 1974 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Rajshahi University, Institute of Bangladesh Studies (76-14-11), 1976 (Box 101, Folder 12)
      Books for Library
    - Satya Wacana University, Research Institute in Social Sciences - Book Grant (75-14-41), 1975 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - University of South Pacific (71-14-6), 1971 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - University of Sri Lanka, Department of Sociology - Book Grant (77-14-24), 1977 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - University of Sri Lanka (77-14-1), 1977 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - University of Sri Lanka (77-14-2), 1977 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - University of Sri Lanka, Institute of Graduate Studies - Book Grant (76-14-6), 1976 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Tamil Nadu Agricultural University - Book Grant (76-14-7), 1976 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - CEDA - Tribhuvan University, Nepal - Equipment (76-14-6), 1976 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - CEDA - Tribhuvan University - Equipment (75-14-44), 1975 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Book and Equipment Grants - Inactive and Refused (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Kasetsart - Arb and Sopin Study Tour (80-14-6), 1980 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Lambung Mangkurat University (78-14-11), 1978 (Box 102, Folder 12)
      Workshop on Coastal Zone Management
    - Bogor Agricultural University (81-14-2), 1981 (Box 103, Folder 1)
      Bungaran Research - Social and Economic Aspects of Agricultural Plantation
    - Diponegoro University (81-14-03), 1981 (Box 103, Folder 2)
      Village Studies Center and Study of Javanese villages
    - Thailand Projects (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Thailand Project (75-15-15), 1975 (Box 103, Folder 4)
      Conference on the Role of Rural Women
    - Thailand Project (75-15-30), 1975 (Box 103, Folder 5)
      Seminar on Agricultural Sector Analysis in Thailand
    - Thailand (71-142-21) - Seminars on Agricultural Development, 1971 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Comparative Experience of Agricultural Development in Developing Countries, Seminar, New Delhi (71-142-14), 1971 October (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Sri Lanka Projects (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Projects - Philippines (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Librarian In-Service Training and Seminar Project, Philippines (72-142-8), 1972 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Summer Session Grad. Assistants Project (72-142-11), 1972 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Staff Member Support at IPB Research Method Workshop (72-15-13), 1972 June-August (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Teaching Agribusiness Management Workshop, Philippines (72-142-7), 1972 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Thailand Project - Seminar on Women in Development (78-15-9), 1978 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Projects - Malaysia (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Tapioca Production and Processing, Malaysia (73-15-2), 1973 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Pakistan Project - Differences in Cotton Production (79-15-4), 1979 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Philippine Project - Study of Philippine Agricultural Productivity and its Determinants (75-15-9), 1975 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Philippine Project - Household Survey of Laguna Province (75-15-10), 1975 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Philippine Project - Study of Technology Transfer Based on Crop Yield Data (75-15-29), 1975 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Philippine Project - Patterns of Labor Utilization on Rice Farms (73-15-44), 1973 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Projects - Indonesia 1973-1974 (Box 105, Folder 1)
    - Trubus Distribution in Indonesia (72-15-41), 1972 (Box 105, Folder 2)
    - Evaluation of Agricultural Development 1969-1972 - Indonesia - D. C. Taylor (72-15-15) (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Five Year Plan Research Support, Indonesia (71-15-7), 1971 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Projects - Indonesia 1973 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Agro-Economic Workshop (72-15-27), 1972 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Indonesian Project - Coastal Ecology (75-15-14), 1975 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - India Project - Analysis of Sources of Growth and Regional Productivity Differentials (75-15-27), 1975 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Indonesian Projects 1975 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Indonesia Project - M. S. Study Tour (75-15-18), 1975 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Indonesian Project - In-Service Data Processing Training (76-15-2), 1976 (Box 106, Folder 2)
    - Indonesian Project - DCT Irrigation Study (76-15-34), 1976 (Box 106, Folder 3)
    - Sinaga English Training (77-15-12), 1977 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Indonesian Project - CGS Study on Income and Employment in Thanjavar District, South India (76-15-33), 1976 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Indonesian Project - CGS Study on Income and Employment in Bojong, Sukabumi Kabupaten (75-15-45) (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Indonesian Projects 1978 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Mellor, John W. - Visiting Fellowship, India, 1958 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Indonesia (Box 107, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence 1959-1961 re: Indonesian CD Project (Box 107, Folder 2)
    - Indonesia Pilot Projects in CD (Box 107, Folder 3)
    - Ford Foundation - Indonesia CD Project, 1958-1963 (Box 107, Folder 4)
    - Ford Foundation - Los Banos Extension, 1962-1964 (Box 108, Folder 1)
    - Ford Foundation - AURP, 1963-1967 (Box 108, Folder 2)
    - Asian Universities Research Program, 1967-1972 (Box 108, Folder 3)
    - Medan Extension Research (Box 108, Folder 4)
  - ADC Grant Proposals, Reviews, and Donor Meetings, 5.2
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund Grant, 1956-1970 (Box 91, Folder 6)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund Grant, 1978 (Box 91, Folder 7)
    - Ford Foundation - Grant Review and Extension, 1976 (Box 92, Folder 1)
    - AID - Coastal Zone Management (Box 92, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Brothers Fund Grant Request, 1977-1978 (Box 92, Folder 3)
    - 1975 Grant Proposal to Rockefeller Foundation (Box 92, Folder 4)
    - AID Grant (Box 93, Folder 1)
    - Japan Foundations, 1977-1981 (Box 93, Folder 2)
    - Japan Foundations - Japan Trips, 1977 February; August; October (Box 93, Folder 3)
    - Ford Foundation Grants, 1972-1977 (Box 94, Folder 1)
    - Ford Foundation Review, 1975-1976 (Box 94, Folder 2-3)
    - AID Indonesia, 1976-1980 (Box 95, Folder 1)
    - 1975 Donors Meeting (Box 95, Folder 2)
    - 1978 Donors Meeting (Box 95, Folder 3)
  - Country Agreements, 5.3
    - Malaysia (Box 108, Folder 5)
    - Philippines (Box 108, Folder 6)
    - Thailand (Box 108, Folder 7)
    - Vietnam (Box 108, Folder 8)
    - India (Box 108, Folder 9)
    - Institut Pertainian Bogor - Indonesia, 1965-1967 (Box 108, Folder 10)
    - Indonesia (Box 109, Folder 1)
    - Malaysia (Box 109, Folder 2)
    - Kasetsart University - Thailand (Box 109, Folder 3)
- Indonesia and Southeast Asia, 1965-1982; 6; 5.97 Cubic Feet 12 letter document boxes and 3 legal document boxes
  - Argo-Economic Survey - Indonesia - Fund Disbursements, 1969-1973 (Box 109, Folder 4)
  - Argo-Economic Survey - Indonesia, 1965-1968 (Box 109, Folder 5)
  - Argo-Economic Survey, 1970 (Box 110, Folder 1)
  - Argo-Economic Survey, 1971 (Box 110, Folder 2)
  - Argo-Economic Survey - Correspondence and Reports - Collier, 1968-1974 (Box 110, Folder 3)
  - Argo-Economic Survey, 1965-1967 (Box 110, Folder 4)
  - Argo-Economic Survey - Ford Foundation, 1973-1975 (Box 110, Folder 5)
  - Argo-Economic Survey History by W. L. Collier 1976 (Box 111, Folder 1)
  - Argo-Economic Survey - 1971 Review (Box 111, Folder 2)
  - Argo-Economic Survey, 1969 (Box 111, Folder 3)
  - Argo-Economic Survey, 1968 (Box 112, Folder 1)
  - Argo-Economic Survey - Ford Foundation, 1968-1976 (Box 112, Folder 2-3)
  - Argo-Economic Survey - Reports and Papers (Box 113, Folder 1)
  - Argo-Economic Survey - Reports and Papers - Rural Dynamics (Box 113, Folder 2-3)
  - Argo-Economic Survey - Reports and Papers - Rural Dynamics (Box 114, Folder 1-2)
  - Regional Research and Training Program (RRTP) - Research Grants (Box 114, Folder 3)
  - Rural Development Studies, 1980 (Box 114, Folder 4)
  - Rural Dynamics - Rudolph S. Sinaga (Box 115, Folder 1)
  - Rural Dynamics - Hayami-Kikuchi Consultantcy (Box 115, Folder 2)
  - Ford Foundation Rural Dynamics Project, 1980-1981 (Box 115, Folder 3)
  - Ford Foundation Rural Dynamics, 1978-1979 (Box 115, Folder 4)
  - Ford Foundation Rural Dynamics, 1977-1978 (Box 115, Folder 5)
  - Rural Dynamics, 1976-1977 (Box 115, Folder 6)
  - Rural Dynamics Project, 1975 (Box 115, Folder 7)
  - Ford Foundation 1975 Report Rural Dynamics (Box 115, Folder 8)
  - Rural Dynamics Study, Indonesia (Box 115, Folder 9)
  - Rural Dynamics - Participating Consultants (Box 116, Folder 1)
  - Rural Dynamics Project Reports (Box 116, Folder 2)
  - Consultants - Rural Dynamics Project (Box 116, Folder 3)
  - AESSEA Biennial Conference, 1981 November 3-7 (Box 116, Folder 4)
  - RRTP Irrigation Workshop, Bangkok, 1981 August 17-21 (Box 116, Folder 5)
  - Coastal Zone Management Research Grants, 7.7.27, 7.7.32, 7.7.35 (Box 116, Folder 6)
  - Leela Pathak, PhD Thesis Research (Box 117, Folder 1)
  - Kasetsart University Chat Chamchong Thesis Research (Box 117, Folder 2)
  - Bogor Agricultural University - Economic Potential of Mangrove Swamps, 7.7.19 (Box 117, Folder 3)
  - RRTP Land and Labor Seminar, 1981 (Box 117, Folder 4)
  - RRTP Workshop on Training in Sociology and Anthropology, 1981 (Box 117, Folder 5)
  - Research Priorities for Rural Development in East Java, Brawijaya University, 1977 August (Box 117, Folder 6)
  - Coastal Zone Management Seminar, Kuala Lumpur, 1979 April (Box 117, Folder 7)
  - Symposium on Tropical Ecology, Kuala Lumpur, 1979 April (Box 117, Folder 8)